Facebook ads in 2026 are difficult. With
rising CPMs, increased competition, and
new AI tools to keep up with, the bar is
higher than it's ever been before.
Everyone's making the same claims, and
it feels impossible to stand out. But,
there's one tactic I've noticed a few of
the best marketers are using, and it's
absolutely crushing in ad accounts right
now. And that is speaking to specific
trigger events. See, a trigger event is
the moment a problem stops being
tolerable. It is the exact moment
someone decides they want to solve a
problem. And if you know that, you can
use it in your marketing. Using trigger
events instead of benefits or features
makes customers feel deeply heard and
trusting of you. It puts you in a blue
ocean instead of the same red ocean that
everyone else is fighting for. And it's
why brands that have cracked this, like
Coridor and Resilia and Moongrade, are
seeing success on Meta right now, cuz
they understand this principle. So,
let's actually look at a real example of
this. This is the ad library of Quazi. I
would say they're one of the best brands
with these AI animation ads. If you look
at their ad library right now, they have
490 active ads. Interestingly, they've
almost got half of them as images, but
in terms of ad formats,
AI animation is responsible for a
quarter of their ads. And even more
interestingly, a lot of the ads near the
top of the rank, at least by
impressions, you can see the number one,
number two, number three ads here are
all AI animations that follow this exact
format. And interestingly, as you can
see here, the top ad by impressions is a
10-minute long AI animation ad, which
is crazy, but also not that crazy,
because I am starting to see that more
and more often, especially with older
audiences. When you get this AI
animation ad right, they absolutely
crush. I started following Quazi
in this ad account on Parker on on the
14th of July, and as you can see, it has
been in the top three by impressions
for the entire time since then. So, 10
days in total, which is very impressive.
And again, by the amount of
these that you can see in the top 15,
it's almost like half of the ads in the
top 15, you can probably guess that that
they are working and that's a pretty,
you know, high confidence bet that I
would place that these are working for
Quazi. I can just scroll down here and I
found a bunch more. I'm actually going
to open one up. I'm going to play one
and watch it together because there is a
theme in these ads that focus on the
trigger events instead of the benefits
and features.
>> My mother-in-law
told me I looked [music] exhausted in
front of my husband's entire family last
Thanksgiving. She said it with [music] a
smile on her face like she was
concerned. Sweetheart, are you sleeping?
You look so exhausted. Is [music]
everything okay at home?
14 people [music] at that table. My
husband just kept cutting his turkey.
That was 7 months [music] ago.
And I've heard some version of that
comment at every family [music] event
since Easter. You need a vacation.
Mother's Day, you seem so drained.
>> And you get the point. So, instead of
starting off by focusing on benefits or
features, they talked about a specific
trigger event that happened in the
prospect's life. So, while they might
feel that embarrassment or shame, they
also feel deeply heard by the brand cuz
they'll be like, "Wow, like you guys
actually understand. This is This is
something that I've gone through."
And these AI animation ads are such a
great way to
to tell that story. I'm not going to
play the whole ad through. I'm going to
put a swipe file in the description with
a a bunch of ads like this that that
focus on trigger events and they are are
AI animation ads. But, they all follow
the same structure. It's always the
trigger event to start off and then it
like really agitates the problem as it
it was you know, did there. It talked
about the different events that she had,
you know, said had someone say to her
that she doesn't look herself. Then they
discover the product. A friend
recommended me this. And then it talks
about the mechanism, how like this is
different to everything she tried before
and then eventually the payoff, you
know, whether it for this this it might
be her mother saying that
uh know, she looks great now. Her
mother-in-law said she looks great now.
So, they all follow the same structure,
which you can by the way take this and
then just uh put it into Cloud Code and
say, "Hey, go and make an a final
trigger event and then go and uh make
this for my brand." But, it's all the
same structure, uh which is like makes
these ads really easy to create if you
can start like uncovering different um
uh different uh trigger events from your
prospects. And here's the swipe file I
was talking about. I've got like 30 of
these uh inside of here. What you'll
notice is that a lot of these are um
are Suno songs.
>> I went through my wife's phone while she
was sleeping. [music] I shouldn't have,
but I knew something was wrong.
>> Again, specific trigger event. Uh and
it's a it's a Suno song. So, they've
actually created these on Suno. So, you
can go and make the lyrics on Cloud and
then just plug it into Suno uh and you
are good to go. You can then go and take
that, animate it in Kling 3.0 uh or
SeeDance, and then actually go and turn
it into an ad. I've done that in a video
before. I'm going to link that video. If
you go to the towards the back end of
this video here and or there,
uh then it will um it will show you me
going through that process and creating
one of these ads, but you know, they're
they're super easy to create if you use
Hixfeld and you use Suno to to uh go and
make these. And you might be thinking,
"Oh, well, like I'm not a supplement
brand or I don't have like as clear of a
uh a wound to to hit here." But, I
guarantee you, if you are a
problem-solution brand, you have some
sort of problem-solution angle, you will
have a way to zero in on a trigger event
and make an ad like this out of it. Here
are some examples that I've seen um on
uh in ad libraries that I've been um
looking at. Uh for acne treatment, I
started ang- I I started angling my face
in photos before I turned 16. For teeth
whitening, it might be, "Nobody told me
to stop smiling in photos, I just did."
For snoring, it might be, "My wife
started sleeping in the guest room."
Like, it doesn't have to be as direct as
like, "Oh, my wife left me." But,
genuinely, I've seen all sorts of
products advertised through this method.
I've seen skin care. I've seen
supplements. I saw a toothbrush. I saw a
toothbrush ad the other day
uh that had an angle with a specific
trigger event and went sell the
toothbrush and it was like a second in
second in their ad library
by impression. So, you know, you can do
this for anything as long as you as long
as you have some sort of problem
solution and I mean this one is um
this one is skin care I believe and it
brings in yeah, it brings in the um
the product around 2 minutes. You
wouldn't have thought oh, you can sell
skin care by talking about how your
mother-in-law thought you look
exhausted, but you can. You can and
these do work really well, especially if
you get the right trigger events from
uh like to to start the ads and the cool
thing is you don't have to invent
trigger events. You can literally take
them from your customers. In fact, if
you have customer reviews or ad comments
or post purchase surveys, in many cases
customers will tell you their specific
trigger events. Look at the longest
customer reviews you've got or the most
emotive customer reviews you've got. In
fact, I'm actually going to show you an
example of a actual chat that I had with
Claude Code uh the other day. So, this
is a brand called Open Farm. They are a
healthy dog food brand. Uh I basically
just asked for specific and detailed
trigger events. You can use a a lot more
simple of a prompt than this. I just got
Claude to give me this prompt. If you
want it, I'll put it in the description.
And I was getting it to do this through
the Parker MCP. So, I have everything
hooked up in Parker in the back end uh
that has all of my customer reviews,
post purchase surveys, ad comments,
organic ad libraries, competitors, ad
account, etc. etc. etc. Uh so, it knows
everything about my brand.
And I said find me trigger events and
this is what it came up with. So,
first of all,
it found this customer review saying my
wonderful German Shepherd is so picky,
she would rather go hungry than eat
something she doesn't like.
Uh that's a great trigger event. Like
the idea of a like your your dog or your
your to be specific your German Shepherd
like rather starving than eating and you
crying next to the food bowl. Like
I mean that's a a freaking powerful
uh trigger event right there that you
could easily use. So, again, doesn't
have to be as as, you know, direct as
the kind of,
you know, the the ones I was showing you
like the the my wife left me type ones
I'm sure like a lot of you guys have
seen on your feed. Um
Another one here.
Uh
for years we couldn't find a a good dog
food for it to help our Yorkie from
chewing off his paws. So, this dog is
chewing off his paws and the trigger
event they suggested is, you know, 2:00
a.m. and the whole household could hear
him chewing off his paws again, which,
you know, again, that's a that's a
really good trigger event. I don't know
what the rest of these, but, you know,
if they're as good as that, then,
uh you know, that would be great. So,
you absolutely could turn both of these
into AI animation as they're both really
solid trigger events. And and they're in
your customer reviews. You don't have to
lie. You don't have to make up stories
here. Go to your customers and uh just
listen to what they're saying. What
they're telling you. What specific
trigger events. The more specific and
detailed, the better. And don't worry
about isolating uh you know, certain
personas or trigger events here cuz if
there are other ones, you can just make
ads for them as well with that trigger
event. Now, you may recognize that this
is a playbook that has been borrowed
from other ad formats, which means that,
you know, these formats are very
interchangeable. The copy that you use
for a AI animation ad, like the one that
we looked at earlier, is very similar to
the copy that you can use for the
primary text of a native ad and also
very similar to the copy that you can
use for a script of a Yappa ad. So,
actually, what we do is when we find one
of these that works in one of these
formats, you can just take it and hand
it to a creator to go and turn it into a
Yappa or turn it into a native ad. Or if
you've got a Yappa, for example, you can
go and turn it into an AI animation and
native ad. These formats work really
well interchangeably and you can take
one of them
uh when you've got something that works
and you can literally just go and make
it across all formats. And that's a way
to extend the lifespan of a creative.
That's what many times for us
uh in the past. Quasi themselves, as I
said, are very good at these AI
animation ads they have a 125 different
variations of AI animation ads in their
library currently and they do that by
focusing on different trigger events.
Now a lot of theirs are kind of revenge
based just because of the nature of the
product. So, you know, for example, for
them, you know, they have, you know, at
63 I ran into my ex-husband at Target
and there were a bunch of different
variations of
running into an ex-husband and them
trying to get revenge on them.
Overhearing the mother-in-law telling
you that you look exhausted, which is
the one that we saw.
Haven't slept in 72 hours and I I look
and feel horrible. I found a text
message that ended my marriage while
making my morning coffee. I almost
refused to be my daughter's wedding. All
of these are different entry points,
different trigger events that will
resonate with different people and all
of them could be their own story lines
for
air animation ads, which, you know, as
you can see, is is why that they've got
so many and they're so successful at
this
and there's so many of them at the top
of their ad library. So, it's all about
finding those different trigger events
from your voice of customer and then
using that as the foundation for your ad
scripts. As well as swapping the trigger
around, you can also do other things.
You can swap the character.
You guys do a lot of different call
outs. Here it says age
at 63. You could, you know, swap the
different characters around to appeal to
different personas in your audience and
you can also swap the format around as
we spoke about. So, there are different
ways to scale this ad format
to make sure that you can increase your
volume and have more shots at goal
by focusing on trigger events. So, let's
talk about how to use this for your
brand. First thing you're going to do is
you're going to mine your customer voice
of customer for trigger events. You're
going to look through your ad comments,
post purchase surveys, Reddit, customer
reviews, etc. Find the different trigger
events. You can do this inside of Clod
by pulling in everything manually. I
prefer to do it inside of Parker.
Well, I prefer to do it inside of Clod
via the Parker MCP just because, as we
said, it already has all of this data
pulled in in real time. I don't have to
worry about pulling in loads of
different MCPs and APIs. It'll pull
through in real time, which is perfect
for me cuz I just want to use one tool
that I rely on inside of Claude. Um and
it also has all of the different ad
libraries
uh scraped and AI tagged for me already
uh and sort by impression, so I can
literally uh go into Claude code and say
I want to find like you can literally go
and take the transcript for this video,
put it into Claude code, say I want to
find more ads like this, more ads like
Quasi's ads that have AI animations and
are emotion-led storytelling ads. Um go
and find me a bunch more in the database
and it'll go and query that and it'll go
and return you ads. This is literally
what it did to me cuz I was doing this
uh as I was preparing for this video cuz
I was trying to find more inspo. I did
this and it came up with a list of uh
different brands and then I said go and
build my swipe file inside of Parker and
and now I have this swipe file that I'm
sharing with you guys that was
completely built out by Claude code in
the Parker MCP. So, if you ever want to
find more uh ads in a certain uh for a
certain format or or
anything that you want, you can just
query it through Claude or you can go to
the discovery page and you can, you
know, say for example here, I want uh
ads that are above 10 minutes that are
AI animation ads and it'll pull up all
of them sort by impression so you can
see the ones that are performing. So,
yeah, uh if you want this swipe file, uh
please um go to the description because
I'm going to put it there. Uh Parker
built the whole thing. Parker also built
uh all of these slides as well. I did
the analysis on Quasi. And if you're not
using the Parker MCP and the Parker
brand at this point, you know, you are
seriously missing out on like the chance
to truly become a 10x marketer cuz I
literally I'm spending all day every day
prompting inside of Claude code and
Codex with it right now. It's so much
fun and I'm getting so so much done.
Um if you want to go and give it a try,
uh have a Parker account so you can
connect the MCP, then I'm giving you a
free month link in the description just
for you guys um to try out completely
risk-free. If you like it, great. If
not, then, you know, no harm, no foul.
Um and if you appreciate this video, uh
then like, comment, subscribe. Let me
know what you want to see more of in the
comments below. And uh yeah, a lot more
content coming your way. Thanks for
watching, and I will see you in the next
one.